<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>En on Toncy Digital</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in En on Toncy Digital</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:22:52 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Set-top Box</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/stb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:22:52 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/stb/</guid>
      <description> Android Set-top Box The GN-6104 Android Set-top Box delivers high performance with versatile media support including 4K and HDR, advanced connectivity options like dual-band Wi-Fi and Bluetooth 5.0, comprehensive codec compatibility, flexible output options, and customizable configurations for diverse business needs.&#xA;more information </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IPTV Total Solution</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/iptvsystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:22:41 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/iptvsystem/</guid>
      <description>Toncy IPTV Total Solution </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DVB Solution</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/solution/dvb_solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:22:36 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/solution/dvb_solution/</guid>
      <description>DVB Solution Introduction Welcome to the future of broadcasting with our comprehensive Digital Video Broadcasting (DVB) end-to-end solution. From content creation to consumption, we offer a seamless ecosystem that integrates advanced head-end devices, sophisticated software systems, and innovative terminals. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how our solution transforms every step of the broadcasting process.&#xA;Head-End Device Our state-of-the-art head-end device serves as the cornerstone of our DVB solution, incorporating essential components for content processing and distribution:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DVB System</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/dvb_solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:22:36 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/dvb_solution/</guid>
      <description>GOSPELL VisionCrypt® Gospell VisionCrypt is a comprehensive security solution tailored for content providers and broadcast operators across CATV, DTT, and DTH platforms. It facilitates both centralized and distributed deployments, ideal for large-scale pay-TV networks spanning vast geographic areas. In such configurations, one central CAS along with several remote CAS units are employed, all of which are managed and monitored by the central CAS.&#xA;more information DTV Advertisement System The GS-9350 Advertising Broadcast System 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DVB System</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/dvbsystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:22:36 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/dvbsystem/</guid>
      <description>GOSPELL VisionCrypt® Gospell VisionCrypt is a comprehensive security solution tailored for content providers and broadcast operators across CATV, DTT, and DTH platforms. It facilitates both centralized and distributed deployments, ideal for large-scale pay-TV networks spanning vast geographic areas. In such configurations, one central CAS along with several remote CAS units are employed, all of which are managed and monitored by the central CAS.&#xA;more information DTV Advertisement System The GS-9350 Advertising Broadcast System 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DTV Headend</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/dtvheadend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:22:21 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/dtvheadend/</guid>
      <description>GQ-3680 series IPQAM Modulator The Toncy GQ-3680 series is a next-generation, modular, high-density IP QAM product that integrates advanced functions such as TS-over-UDP/RTP, multiplexing, and scrambling into a 1U chassis, capable of supporting up to 72 channels with up to 2G bandwidth per sub-card.&#xA;more information GN-1792 HEVC/AVC Ultra Multi-channel UHD OTT/DVB Transcoder The GN-1792 is a versatile UHD OTT/DVB transcoder supporting HEVC/AVC/MPEG-2 formats, offering mutual H.264/H.265 transcoding, MPEG-2 output, and ultra multi-channel capability to reduce per-channel costs, suitable for a wide range of applications including traditional TV, internet streaming, cloud gaming, AR/VR, and live broadcasting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transmitter</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/transmitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:21:57 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/transmitter/</guid>
      <description> GT-5900A Series Terrestrial Digital Television Broadcasting Transmitter The Toncy GT-5900A series indoor terrestrial digital television broadcasting transmitter operates at 470-700MHz, offering flexible configuration along with Toncy&#39;s trademark high performance, stability, and reliability. Ideal for multi-frequency transmission, it provides extensive coverage, making it perfect for digital TV networks across complex and expansive terrains.&#xA;more information </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRM digital radio headend and receivers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/drm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:21:33 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/drm/</guid>
      <description>Toncy DRM Encoder / Multiplexer The Toncy DRM Encoder / Multiplexer is a highly reliable professional broadcast system for Digital Radio Mondiale. It supports the content and signalling options DRM offers and all interfaces for a smooth integration into the broadcast chain.&#xA;more information GQ-3770 DRM Exciter The Toncy GQ-3770 DRM Modulation Exciter, based on an embedded platform, is equipped with channel coding and OFDM modulation, capable of generating I/Q signals compliant with ETSI ES 201 980 by receiving MDI/DCP streams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRM Modulator</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/drm_modulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 13:29:16 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/drm_modulator/</guid>
      <description>GQ-3770 DRM Modulator The Toncy GQ-3770 DRM Modulator is a core device for DRM baseband processing based on an embedded platform. It is equipped with channel coding and OFDM modulation capabilities, capable of receiving MDI/DCP streams from DRM encoding multiplexers to generate I/Q signals in compliance with ETSI ES 201 980 standards. The Modulator includes functionality to reduce the peak-to-average power ratio (PAPR), effectively lowering the PAPR of OFDM signals, thus enhancing the output capability and efficiency of transmitters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/aboutus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:38:54 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/aboutus/</guid>
      <description>About Chengdu Toncy Digital Systems Co., Ltd. Established on July 11, 2005, Chengdu Toncy Digital Systems Co., Ltd. is a wholly-owned subsidiary of Gospell Digital Technology Co., Ltd. (stock code: 002848), controlled by the State-owned Assets Supervision and Administration Commission of Weifang City, Shandong Province. Our headquarters is strategically located in the Jinniu District of Chengdu, China. As a national high-tech enterprise and software company, we pride ourselves on holding CMMI Level 3 and ISO9001 quality system certifications, reflecting our commitment to the highest standards of quality and innovation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/news_index/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:37:17 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/news_index/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MW/SW Station DRM Digitalization</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/solution/drm_upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:36:16 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/solution/drm_upgrade/</guid>
      <description>Toncy has launched an end-to-end DRM digital broadcasting solution, specifically designed for the digital transformation of MW/SW broadcast stations, covering everything from DRM front-end systems to various types of terminal receivers. With Toncy&amp;rsquo;s support, this one-stop solution facilitates a smooth transition from traditional to digital broadcasting for stations and operators.&#xA;The headend system includes:&#xA;DRM Encoder Multiplexer: Responsible for encoding audio and data content and generating multiplex streams according to DRM standards, ensuring high-quality transmission of broadcast content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IPTV Total Solution</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/solution/iptv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:35:39 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/solution/iptv/</guid>
      <description>Toncy IPTV Total Solution Toncy provides a Total IPTV Solution with a complete package tailored for operators without prior IPTVexperience. This comprehensive solution includes a user-friendly Content Management System, robust DRM system, live streaming, video on demand, time-shift capabilities, catch-up TV, user management, CDN, Android set-top boxes, IPTV player, and a customizable launcher.&#xA;Importantly, the existing program sources from most DVB systems can be seamlessly integrated into our IPTV system. Additionally, we provide professional transcoding equipment to effortlessly convert program sources into the input streams required for IPTV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Set-top Box</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/android_stb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:35:09 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/android_stb/</guid>
      <description>GN-6104 Android Set-top Box&#xA;High Performance: Offers exceptional functionality and flexibility, with multiple configurations to meet diverse business needs. Advanced Connectivity: Includes dual-band Wi-Fi (802.11 a/b/g/n/ac), Bluetooth 5.0, and a built-in antenna for robust network connections. Versatile Media Support: Supports a wide range of video and audio formats, including 4K and HDR content. Comprehensive Decoding: Compatible with various codecs like H.264 AVC, H.265 HEVC, AV1, and more. Flexible Outputs and Upgrades: Features HDMI 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DVB Set-top Box</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/dvb_stb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:34:56 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/dvb_stb/</guid>
      <description>DVB Set-top Box At Gospell, we&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to present our comprehensive selection of DVB Set-Top Boxes (STBs) designed to revolutionize your entertainment experience. Our range encompasses a variety of models, each equipped with powerful chipsets and customizable configurations to meet your unique needs.&#xA;Advanced Chipsets, Enhanced Security: Our STBs are powered by industry-leading chipsets from ALI, Hisilicon, NationalChip, and more, ensuring seamless performance and robust security features.&#xA;CAS Integration for Enhanced Security: Benefit from seamless integration with leading Conditional Access Systems (CAS) providers such as Gospell , Sumavision, ABV, and others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRM Emergency Receiver</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/drm_ewf_receiver/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:34:42 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/drm_ewf_receiver/</guid>
      <description>DRM Emergency Receiver In the field of emergency broadcasting, Digital Radio Mondiale (DRM) exhibits significant advantages, particularly its ability to operate on medium wave and shortwave bands, enabling long-range broadcasting capabilities. This means that DRM broadcasts do not rely on local infrastructure, such as electricity and network services, making them unaffected by local disasters. When disasters occur, local broadcasting systems may cease to function due to personnel evacuations or infrastructure damage, but DRM can transmit emergency broadcast content directly from transmitters hundreds or even thousands of kilometers away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRM Car Receivers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/drm_car_receiver/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:34:30 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/drm_car_receiver/</guid>
      <description>DRM Car Receivers We have launched a diversified range of in-car DRM receiver solutions, which include both OEM integration modules and aftermarket receiver units, to meet the varying needs of different vehicle types and users. By offering a new digital broadcasting experience, we have enhanced the audio quality of in-car broadcasts, the selection of broadcast services, and the richness of data services, including news, weather forecasts, traffic updates, and emergency alerts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRM Consumer Receivers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/drm_consumer_receiver/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:34:17 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/drm_consumer_receiver/</guid>
      <description>DRM Consumer Receivers Since 2006, the digital audio broadcasting research and development team at Toncy has been dedicated to advancing digital broadcasting technology. We specialize in the development, manufacturing, and sales of digital audio broadcast receivers. Our team has successfully launched several consumer-grade digital audio receivers, including some global firsts that have pioneered new territories in digital audio broadcast receiver technology.&#xA;Our consumer receivers are designed for radio enthusiasts and everyday users alike, suitable for home use and portable enough for daily carry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRM Encoder / Multiplexer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/drm_encoder/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:33:42 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/drm_encoder/</guid>
      <description>Toncy DRM Encoder / Multiplexer The Toncy DRM Encoder / Multiplexer is a highly reliable professional broadcast system for Digital Radio Mondiale. It supports the content and signalling options DRM offers and all interfaces for a smooth integration into the broadcast chain.&#xA;The system is typically located in the studio, at a play-out center or at the transmitter site – with full remote control for administration and data provision, enabling cloud-based operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DTV Advertisement System</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/dtv_ad_system/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:33:26 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/dtv_ad_system/</guid>
      <description>GS-9350 Advertising Broadcast System 5.1 GS-9350 Advertising Broadcast System 5.1 is a sophisticated software system capable of inserting various forms of advertisements into digital television streams. These advertisements can include scrolling subtitles in picture format, corner animations, menu images, prompt window images, set-top box startup images, channel change images, program banners, pop-up images, and background images for broadcast programs, as well as startup and menu videos. Through this system, operators can devise and execute advertising strategies, and manage and produce advertising content, ensuring that legitimate advertisements are broadcast across digital television networks according to specific requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iptv</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/iptv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:33:05 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/iptv/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital_rights_management</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/digital_rights_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:32:49 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/digital_rights_management/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOSPELL VisionCrypt®</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/cas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:32:28 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/cas/</guid>
      <description>GOSPELL VisionCrypt® Gospell VisionCrypt is a comprehensive security solution tailored for content providers and broadcast operators across CATV, DTT, and DTH platforms. It facilitates both centralized and distributed deployments, ideal for large-scale pay-TV networks spanning vast geographic areas. In such configurations, one central CAS along with several remote CAS units are employed, all of which are managed and monitored by the central CAS.&#xA;Gospell VisionCrypt CAS is engineered to ensure a completely secure content environment for broadcast operators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Encoder</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/video_encoder/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:32:08 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/video_encoder/</guid>
      <description>GN-1846 Multi-Channel H.264 HD Encoder The GN-1846 Multi-Channel H.264 HD Encoder is a broadcast-quality, cost-effective digital TV encoder. It supports 4/8/12/16/20/24 channels of high-definition, low-bitrate audio and video encoding, with each sub-board handling four channels of audio and video encoding that can be output through a single IP channel. Each channel also supports the HLS (Http Live Stream) live streaming protocol. This product is particularly useful for operators who primarily rely on or purchase content from larger providers but also have some independent content sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DTV Transmitter</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/dtv_transmitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:31:06 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/dtv_transmitter/</guid>
      <description>GT-5900A Series Terrestrial Digital Television Broadcasting Transmitter The Toncy GT-5900A series indoor terrestrial digital television broadcasting transmitter operates within the 470-700MHz frequency range. It features a flexible configuration while maintaining Toncy&amp;rsquo;s hallmark of high performance, exceptional stability, and reliability. This transmitter excels in meeting the demands for multi-frequency transmission and extensive regional coverage. It is particularly well-suited for terrestrial digital TV networks that span complex terrains and broad areas.&#xA;The device boasts an advanced system design, low noise output, high operational efficiency, superior anti-interference capabilities, a compact and simple structure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Transcoder</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/transcoder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 14:33:13 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/transcoder/</guid>
      <description>GN-1792 HEVC/AVC Ultra Multi-channel UHD OTT/DVB Transcoder GN-1792 HEVC/AVC/MPEG-2 ultra multi-channel UHD OTT/DVB transcoder can flexibly support DVB live broadcast and streaming media transcoding. It supports H.264/H.265 mutual transcoding and to trancode to MPEG-2, and can effectively reduce the video bit rate, and also supports traditional equipment. This device supports ultra multi-channel, which can greatly reduce the cost of single-channel usage and maintenance. It is suitable for traditional TV stream transcoding and Internet stream media, cloud game, AR/VR, video conferencing, home monitoring, social video call, network real-time live broadcast and other application scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IPQAM Modulator</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/ipqam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 14:28:43 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/ipqam/</guid>
      <description>GQ-3680 series IPQAM Modulator The Toncy GQ-3680 series represents a new generation of modular, high-density IP QAM products, integrating multiple functions within a compact 1U chassis. These functions include TS-over-UDP/RTP input and output, TS stream multiplexing, scrambling, PSI/SI processing, and modulation capabilities for 16/32/64/128/256QAM. When equipped with three plug-and-play 16-channel or 24-channel QAM module sub-cards, the GQ-3680 can support up to 48 or 72 modulated outputs, with each sub-card handling up to 2G bandwidth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Categories Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/categories-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 21:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/categories-post/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a post with multiple categories in the frontmatter:&#xA;categories = [&amp;quot;programming&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;lorem&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;pseudo&amp;quot;] Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. In mauris nulla, vestibulum vel auctor sed, posuere eu lorem. Aliquam consequat augue ut accumsan mollis. Suspendisse malesuada sodales tincidunt. Vivamus sed erat ac augue bibendum porta sed id ipsum. Ut mollis mauris eget ligula sagittis cursus. Aliquam id pharetra tellus. Pellentesque sed tempus risus. Proin id hendrerit ante. Vestibulum vitae urna ut mauris ultricies dignissim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linked post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/linked-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/linked-post/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a linked post in the menu. You can add other posts by adding the following line to the frontmatter:&#xA;menu = &amp;quot;main&amp;quot; Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. In mauris nulla, vestibulum vel auctor sed, posuere eu lorem. Aliquam consequat augue ut accumsan mollis. Suspendisse malesuada sodales tincidunt. Vivamus sed erat ac augue bibendum porta sed id ipsum. Ut mollis mauris eget ligula sagittis cursus. Aliquam id pharetra tellus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go is for lovers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/go-is-for-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/go-is-for-lovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.&#xA;This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugo is for lovers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/hugo-is-for-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/hugo-is-for-lovers/</guid>
      <description>This is the summary Goto &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/spf13/hugo/releases&#34;&gt;hugo releases&lt;/a&gt; and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture. Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step. More complete instructions are available at &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/overview/installing/&#34;&gt;installing hugo&lt;/a&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a new theme</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.&#xA;We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you If you have any inquiries about our solutions, products, or services, please do not hesitate to contact us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.&#xA;1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrate from Jekyll</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like&#xA;▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png should become&#xA;▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
